A few days ago, the entire family together had
almost completed the back wall of our bathroom.
But there was still some
work left which we all are going to complete together today.
For which I also
wore my labourer's uniform and came to the
side.  Last time I was
carrying a tray full of stones and giving it upstairs.  But this time
I gave this work to my brother and I was
holding it from above and putting stones in the back wall.
Papa was
working on arranging the stones properly.  Last time
Papa had almost completed the wall.
Only stones were left to be filled here.
But after that, both mom and dad fell
ill and the work stopped there.
But today we complete it.
And after this, Papa also starts masonry of the side wall.
Papa completed the masonry from the inside and then made a platform
here to do the masonry from the outside the next day.
Rest of the friends,
what things do you like in my videos?